Guide to the Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files 1922-2004 (bulk, 1923-1989) MS 3009-RG 21
New-York Historical Society
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Space Tour (Offsite-box 3512, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: What's Going On... (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: World War I Prints (Offsite-box 3544, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: World's Fair (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: World's Fair: Life Previews the 1964 World's Fair (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Year-End Issue, "The Bible" (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Year-End Issue, "The Bible" (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1964: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Ads: "Advertising in Life" (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Ads: Inserts (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Ads: "Spot Life" (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 8-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Automotive Industry Booklet (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Churchill Funeral (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Circulation (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Job Index (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: "Live Better Electrically" (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Market Research and TV: Bureau of Labor Statistics, "Consumer Expenditure / Magazine Coverage" (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Market Research and TV: Jaffe Reports (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Market Research and TV: National Industrial Conference Board (NICB), "Expenditure Patterns of the American Family" (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Market Research and TV: National Industrial Conference Board (NICB), "Market Profiles of Consumer Products" (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Market Research and TV: Nowland Studies (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 10-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Market Research and TV: Simmons, Coverage and Cost per Thousand (CPM) (Offsite-box 3548, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Market Research and TV: Survey of Surveys (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 13-17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Media Mix (Offsite-box 3549, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: National Football League Tie-In (Offsite-box 3513, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 1-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Regional Special Edition, 1965 May 7 (Offsite-box 3549, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Spot Life Program (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Vietnam (Offsite-box 3549, Folder 3-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: What's Going On... (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Year-End Issue, "The City" (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1965: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3549, Folder 6-7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Ads: "Best Foot Forward" (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Ads: "Challenge" (Offsite-box 3549, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3549, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Ads: Inserts (Offsite-box 3549, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3549, Folder 11-13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Automotive Industry Booklet (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Campbell Soups (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Circulation (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 13-14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Job Index (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Market Research and TV: Simmons, Coverage and Cost per Thousand (CPM) (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Market Research and TV: Simmons, Product Usage Report (Offsite-box 3514, Folder 16-17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3515, Folder 1-8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: "Media Balance" (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 3-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: "Modern Home Manual" (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: National Football League Tie-In (Offsite-box 3515, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: National Football League Tie-In (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: "On Time" (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: "Prime Time Trends" (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Quality Story (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3515, Folder 10-13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: "The Romans" (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Sales Marketing Representatives (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Space Tour (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Teenage Promotion (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: What's Going On... (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Year-End Issue, "Photography" (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 7-8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1966: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3550, Folder 12-14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3551, Folder 1-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Cat Prints (Offsite-box 3551, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Circulation (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 9-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Creative Staff (Offsite-box 3551, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Food Calendars (Offsite-box 3551, Folder 7-8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Job Index (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Market Research and TV: Household Brand Decision-Making (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Market Research and TV: Lerner Study (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Market Research and TV: Morplan Page-Size Study (Eye-Camera) (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Market Research and TV: Politz Study (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Market Research and TV: Simmons, Coverage and Cost per Thousand (CPM) (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 16-17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Market Research and TV: Simmons, Life vs. Newspapers Study (Offsite-box 3516, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3517, Folder 1-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Marketing Expenditures Patterns (Offsite-box 3551, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: "Media Balance" (Offsite-box 3551, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Merchandising: Golf Markers (Offsite-box 3517, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: National Football League Tie-In (Offsite-box 3551, Folder 11-12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: New Products (Offsite-box 3551, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: "Power of Print in Media Balance" (Offsite-box 3551, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3517, Folder 8-13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: "To Help You Sell Life" (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Year-End Issue, "Wide World" (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1967: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 1-2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Ads: Inserts (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Ads: "Life: Consider the Alternative" (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Circulation (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Food Calendars (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Job Index (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Managers Meeting (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Market Research and TV: Simmons, Coverage and Cost per Thousand (CPM) (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous, 1968 January-August (Offsite-box 3518, Folder 11-18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous, 1968 September-December (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 1-2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: National Football League Tie-In (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Quaker State (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 3-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: This is Life Radio Program (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 6-7)
  1 phonograph record (33 1/3 rpm); 7 in. (5 copies); Label on Side 1 and 2: "This is Life. This week's great stories in LIFE on RADIO today."
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: "To Help You Sell Life" (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Year-End Issue, "Picasso" (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 10-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1968: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 9-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Ads: "Come to Life" (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 11-15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Ads: Inserts (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3552, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Alcoa (Offsite-box 3553, Folder 1-2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: "Apollo" (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Circulation (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 13-14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Circulation Book (Offsite-box 3553, Folder 3-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Del Monte (Offsite-box 3553, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Job Index (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: "Life Works" (Result Stories) (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Market Research and TV: Grudin/Appel (Offsite-box 3519, Folder 17-18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Market Research and TV: Politz (Offsite-box 3520, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Market Research and TV: Psychographics (Offsite-box 3520, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Market Research and TV: Simmons, Circulation Study (Offsite-box 3520, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Market Research and TV: Simmons, Cost per Thousand (CPM) Study (Offsite-box 3520, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3520, Folder 5-12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Moon Landing (Offsite-box 3553, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: National Football League Tie-In (Offsite-box 3520, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Posters (Offsite-box 3520, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 1-3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 4)
  1 phonograph record (33 1/3 rpm); 7 in. On label: "'Never Give Up!' narrated by Eddie Lawrence. Penina Golf Hotel, Portugal. 1969."
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969-1972: Service to Advertisers Samples (Offsite-box 3553, Folder 8-12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Television "Clutter" (Reference Material) (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Year-End Issue, "The Sixties" (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1969: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3553, Folder 13-15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Ads: "Come to Life" (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Ads: "Tables are Turning" (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 4-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Circulation (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Crown Zellerbach, "The Frozen Moment" (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 6-7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Dialogue Marketing (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Job Index (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970-1972: Market Research and TV: Alcoa Ad Effectiveness Before and After Study (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Market Research and TV: General Foods (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Market Research and TV: Grudin/Appel/Haley (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 13-14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Market Research and TV: The Wine Market (Offsite-box 3521, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3522, Folder 1-14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: National Football League Tie-In (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: National Football League Tie-In (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 1)
  1 film reel; 8 mm. On label: "Buz Blynn. Life/NFLP 1970." On container: "Life/NFLP 1970. Buz Blynn."
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Presentation: "Toward Better Media Comparisons" Kodak Slide Carousel (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 2)
  Contains "Kodak Carousel Universal Slide Tray" with photographic slides.
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Rates and Specials (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 3-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Year-End Issue, "Photography Contest" (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 6-7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1970: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 9-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: "The Brain" Special Series (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Circulation (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 8-9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Job Index (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: "Life Works" (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Market Research and TV: Gruden/Appel, General Electric Cluster (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Market Research and TV: Harris, Consumerism Study (Offsite-box 3523, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Market Research and TV: Magazine Comparison Series (Offsite-box 3524, Folder 1-2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3524, Folder 3-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Olympics (Offsite-box 3524, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Quality Book (Offsite-box 3524, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3524, Folder 14-16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3524, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Space Lab (Sales Training Program) (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Year-End Issue, "Children" (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 3-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1971: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Beach Party (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Circulation (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Double Year-End Issue (Offsite-box 3554, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: "Edit Table Contents Leaflet" (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Job Index (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Life Frames (Offsite-box 3555, Folder 1-2)
  Includes Life-branded picture frame.
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: "Life Means Business" (Offsite-box 3555, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Automotive (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 9-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Bowdren, Polaroid Study (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Bristol Myers Sales Tests (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Dichter, Consumer Motivations (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: General Foods Reprise (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Harris, Consumerism Study (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 15-18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Life's Media Market Guide (Offsite-box 3525, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Magazine Comparison Series (Offsite-box 3526, Folder 1-2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Simmons, Demographic Study (Offsite-box 3526, Folder 3-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Simmons, State Audience Study (Offsite-box 3526, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3526, Folder 7-13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: "The Marketing Gap" (Offsite-box 3555, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Merchandising (Offsite-box 3526, Folder 14)
  Includes Life-branded oversize "Fast Close" pin.
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Merchandising (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: National Tire Dealers and Retreaders Association (NTDRA) Scholarship Award (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Panda Prints (Offsite-box 3555, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Poster Contest Mailings (Offsite-box 3555, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Progress Reports (Offsite-box 3555, Folder 7-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Rates and Special Units (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Special Units (Offsite-box 3556, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Year-End Issue, "Christmas" (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 5-7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1972: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3556, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1973: Beach Party Merchandising (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 6-17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1973: Merchandising (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1978: General (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1978: General (Offsite-box 3556, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1988: Reprint, "John F. Kennedy Memorial Edition" (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 20)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1990-2000: General (Offsite-box 3556, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1990-1995: Calendars (Offsite-box 3556, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1991: Issue, "JFK: Why We Still Care", 1991 December (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 21)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1992: Bicentennial Issue, "The White House, 1792-1992", 1992 October 30 (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 22)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1992: Collector's Edition, "The Big Board" (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 23-24)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1994: Book-a-zine, "Earth's Wonders" (Offsite-box 3527, Folder 25)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1994: Collector's Edition, "The Roots of Country Music", 1994 September 1 (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1994: Special Commemorative Edition, "Remember Jackie: A Life in Pictures", 1994 July 15 (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1995: Collector's Edition, "Elvis: On His 60th Birthday, A Celebration in Pictures", 1995 February 10 (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1996: Collector's Edition, 60th Anniversary, 1996 October (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1996: Collector's Edition, "Hot for the Road" (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1996: Commemorative Edition, 60th Anniversary (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1996: Special Issue, "The 50 Most Influential Baby Boomers", 1996 July 15 (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1997: Collector's Edition, "Celebrating Our Heroes", 1997 May 5 (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1997: Special Double Issue, "The Millennium" (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1997: Special Issue, "The Kennedys: The Third Generation", 1997 July 7 (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1998: Book-a-zine, "The Best of Life Carries On" (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1998: Book-a-zine, "Days that Rocked the World" (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1998: Collector's Edition, "The Eisie Issue: The Best Magazine Photography of the Year" (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1998: Collector's Edition, "To the Moon and Back" (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1998: Issue, "God", 1998 December (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1998: Issue, "Medical Miracles for the Next Millennium" (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1998: Special Royals Issue, "The Boy Who Will Be King" (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1999: Collector's Edition, "The 1999 Eisies: The Best Magazine Photography of the Year" (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1999: Commemorative Issue, "The Oscars Then and Now", 1999 March (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1999: Media Kits, 1999 March (Offsite-box 3528, Folder 20-21)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: Contracts: Terminated Services [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Offsite-box R55, Folder 50)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: Advertised-in-Life House Ads, A-D, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3556, Folder 6-9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: Master Files: Advertised-in-Life House Ads, F-T, 1962-1966 (Offsite-box 3557, Folder 1-4)